[
   {
      "question":"How old are you?",
      "answer":"12"
   },
   {
      "question":"Do you have any pre-existing condition?",
      "answer":"no"
   },
   {
      "question":"When do you usually feel hungry?",
      "answer":"4 hrs after the previous meal"
   },
   {
      "question":"How often do you have diarrhoea, gas or constipation?",
      "answer":"Rarely"
   },
   {
      "question":"Do you face difficulty sleeping?",
      "answer":"Rarely"
   },
   {
      "question":"Do you get restless or agitated?",
      "answer":"Rarely"
   },
   {
      "question":"Do you still feel exhausted after getting enough sleep?",
      "answer":"No"
   },
   {
      "question":"How often do you catch cold/flu?",
      "answer":"No"
   },
   {
      "question":"How long does it take for you to recover from flu or cold?",
      "answer":"5 days"
   },
   {
      "question":"Do you have any body itch/allergies?",
      "answer":"No"
   },
   {
      "question":"Have you been back to your doctor for treatment of a problem with your wound?",
      "answer":"No"
   },
   {
      "question":"Do you suffer from recurrent or usual infections?",
      "answer":"Rarely"
   },
   {
      "question":"How often do you use antibiotic?",
      "answer":"Rarely"
   },
   {
      "question":"Think carefully and select the activity that, if you performed, would typically cause fatigue, shortness of breath, chest discomfort, or otherwise cause you to want to stop",
      "answer":"After intensive workout for 30 mins or more"
   }
]